

PROFILE

Experienced Project Coordinator and Administrator with a demonstrated history of working in the architecture & planning industry. Strong information technology professional skilled in Microsoft Word, Excel, Access, Sage, Quick Books, with organization skills, management, teamwork, and leadership experience.

In my personal life, I enjoy hosting and networking as I love bringing people together. I also thoroughly enjoy creative projects to keep myself busy during my downtime.

CONTACT

PHONE:

416-898-7821

EMAIL:

natalie.clinton@hotmail.com

HOBBIES

Camping
Pilates
Jewelry Making
Cooking
Video Gaming
DIY/Crafting

CERTIFICATIONS

Joint Health and Safety Committee Smart Serve Ontario

NATALIE CLINTON

PROJECT COORDINATOR

EDUCATION

University of Toronto – Full Stack Coding

February 2024 – August 2024

Creativity and problem solving are two of my favorite ways of expressing myself and I wanted to learn a new medium to be able to do so in personal and work-related settings.

Centennial College – International Business (Marketing)

September 2017 – January 2020

Learned the basics of business, from accounting to communications. Out of thousands of applicants, I was chosen to go on a trip which was an all-expense paid marketing start up selling beers in Belgium.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Gray's Landscaping and Snow Removal Inc. – Project Coordinator June 2023 – Current

Ensuring the successful planning, execution, and completion of landscape construction projects. Collaborating with project managers, contractors, and clients to coordinate all aspects of the project, from initial planning to final delivery.

Salivan Landscape Inc. – Project Coordinator, Admin, AP

May 2017 – June 2023

Same as the above, with the addition of monitoring office needs such as health and safety requirements and helping accounting with receiving, processing, verifying, and reconciling invoices.

Philthy Philly's Poutinery – Cashier and Service Worker

September 2015 - 2017

Responsible for preparing, serving food, monitoring stock levels in the kitchen area and cleaning up any messes during service. Easily completed multiple tasks in a fast-paced environment.

SKILLS

- Technical Writing
- Customer Relationship Management
- Risk Management
- Leadership and Team Management
- Conflict Resolution

- Time Management
- Quality Assurance
- Cash Handling
- Physical Stamina
- Communication Skills
- Multitasking
- Problem Solving